<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/red/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Red on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum. Deserunt esse cillum Lorem non magna adipisicing mollit amet consequat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia. Velit id fugiat occaecat do tempor. Sit officia Lorem aliquip eu deserunt consectetur. Aute proident deserunt in nulla aliquip dolore ipsum Lorem ut cupidatat consectetur sit sint laborum. Esse cupidatat sit sint sunt tempor exercitation deserunt. Labore dolor duis laborum est do nisi ut veniam dolor et nostrud nostrud.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serving Your Home Server with True Fiber Internet Without a Static IP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/serve-home-server-with-true-fiber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/serve-home-server-with-true-fiber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;problem-description&#34;&gt;Problem Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I switched to a new internet service provider in Thailand called &amp;ldquo;True.&amp;rdquo; The name is quite inconvenient for searching solutions related to their services due to its common use as a Boolean variable or word. Previously, I was using &amp;ldquo;AIS,&amp;rdquo; which was affordable, costing only 200B to get a static IP. However, with &amp;ldquo;True,&amp;rdquo; obtaining a static IP for my home server has become quite expensive, costing around 1000B.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
